I guess
Think they're all still in the back on the last one. Oh, I actually kick my foot about
So you're gonna let your feet down your channel psyche like you're gonna let her continue because now she's gonna take down your channel
And you're doing shit for him to get strike. So I mean if you're gonna say something about why you gotta say something about you too
Cuz you shouldn't play it on this fucking thing
You know she's fucking pissed about it
He can't get strike for that. Well, he's been strike for less shit. So
That's not against you I don't know if he can or can't to be honest with you, but I'm just saying like I mean
That's fake as fuck though for her to be like
Well, don't so sit that's gonna piss her off on a shit. Don't put his son
Do it on yours why do it on his panel
She cuz you're showing shit of all on his panel. That's fake. Well, do the shit on your panel
You ain't got nothing to worry about stupid bitch. Like that's really fake. Well, you're fake bitch
Everything about you is fake bitch
So you want somebody else's face you literally threatened to take down psyches channel for seeing you're really well, you know
Do you remember when you spend madame already spent three hours like bickering with Alexander
Where he abused you and talk shit about you and you actually fly
Well, I'm just telling you you got to cry soon. I'm giving you fuck
You've been crying you've been crying the full time. What the fuck? I've been having a great time. What the fuck now that you're talking to her
Actually, you don't like her anymore. That's really like you definitely don't have no girl code bitch cuz you a man
You think like I would you know where the fuck diamond is fucking shut because you know what I've been having a see you on
I've been fucking screaming fucking going like bitch. You know what you know what let me tell you one thing
You know what's gonna be really sad for you
How do you know
Everybody knows how you call the cops on the page and if I did and so what and if I did not would you know
You're really weird. Maybe I should call the cops on you know
Do it. What are you gonna do? Maybe I should like let like the cops know that you're taking
EBT free services and like filling your whore ass on the street and cash and you're not reporting that
I'm not doing nothing in legal California
But that would don't you fucking mind my fucking business. I only came up here to say one thing
You know, I wanted to come here and tell you one fucking thing
Lesson only difference between me summer and Christine and you is that you will always fucking want a pussy that you can never have
You can never have a pussy
All right, your pussy is not gonna be ever exist and you're always gonna have dick
In your face
Put all the makeup on
Put your hair in little ties and bows and put your stuff off like makeup cake it on for three hours
You're still gonna look like a fucking pig
Is Kevin here Kevin
You know what raising him in cries over me not you he still comes around going
He's talking to them and it's a good
Beta you realize that right
Doesn't realize anything
Oh wow
I would love to hear that
Have you come publicly and said
I
Love you, I love you
What's up, Gotti?
You are like a pathetic diamond, like, really.
You really think that you realize he's only using you to get back to her, right?
You realize that, right?
I mean, you're a man.
You should know when a man is using a woman to get to another woman.
You should know that. You're a man.
And you're a little sad.
I could be a little happy, but I'm still a woman.
I will always be a woman.
It's something you will never be.
You will never be, bitch! You will never be!
Oh, bitch, you won't go the fucking time, bitch. I know you ain't talking.
I know you ain't talking.
You don't fucking, that's what you need, a motherfucker across the street to pet you on the fucking internet, bitch.
And he's doing it to get you, to get, uh, get a juice from the next bit.
But you two got damn slow to realize that.
You get you, that's what you do. You get you, bitch.
From Miguel to Flagging Psyche's channel, now Psyche's third.
Well, I can't be an explainer, she doesn't realize it yet.
I might say something as a joke, but I will never...
If I wanted to flag anybody, I would have like flagged other people that would be streaming every fucking day, alright?
But you know what, Flirty? You sat on that panel with Alex and you would cry.
I didn't cry, but I never cried.
And you took the abuse, and what did you do? You flagged Psyche the next day.
You flagged, you flagged. You're a red flag.
You're a whore!
You're such a great cuss like you're such a great whore you should be walking the blade
Like you're here crying over Sam and you're a little you got a dakin boss and Sam on my cry over me
But nobody will cry over you though and
Here you are your and your you stop on fucking senior your string yard fucking you stop whore
All right, you want to do pictures. Let's listen to pictures. Oh, yeah, you stop fucking string yard whore
Even you step on string are you gonna cry 30 diamond? It's okay. It'll be all good
No, but you're gonna cry
I
Don't know you seem a little
You need a coat from bombing all those places and everything too, but come on go to bed
Like you you're gonna get flagged. Yeah, she's talking about bomb and I'm like
Cuz I'm a I kind of been around summer can
Like no, she's talking about terrific shit, you know, yep
You just watch out psyche
Now if you want to boot me off for her like talking like terrific, I mean go ahead
But she literally is trying to flag you again
Okay, and he's been flagged for transphobic behavior as well
Like I'm not gonna flag him, but I'm just saying he could be flagged for transphobia from what you're trying to him again
We don't give a fuck
You a lame-ass bitch
Stop trying to flag me. I'm not I'm just sitting here like how do people talk
Money she should be making dough, but like she's gonna be up here, right?
Yeah, you ain't gonna check on the track to go and do your shit with I don't need to work the blade
But you was what I got pictures of you on the blade. We're in the green fuck of bikini with your nasty ass belly
I'll hang it out
Corporate CEO like that. You're just like
You're still scared
When you was working to fuck a blade that would never like what two weeks ago bitch. What are you talking about?
Guys, can you like this dream? I got I got I have like it looks like 66 people in the chat only
Uh seven likes and so if you guys can just like the stream for me. Thank you so much
I'm gonna pin my link right now. I'll do it when I
Okay, no problem. No problem. It's already done. I won't fuck up your stream. I'll like it right before I leave
Okay
Hey, so you see we also have these that we have these that you can get these
Points, I don't know. It's a the XP that shows who's the
Most active people in chat. It looks like it looks like a number one Joseph Johnston number two be cash number three
sassy scarlet number four Samantha Avery nor five low-key
Jamie's cowboy
You know, I'm not fake like you beat us. I actually like the stream before I even came up here
Okay, well, thank you. I appreciate that a camera action bureau. You're
Fake I just another time. I'm so sorry
You didn't have the time but you had the time to click on a link where you didn't you couldn't click a thumbs up
I'm sorry, you know you had money
You couldn't click on a thumbs up
I had many opportunities to like my fucking life
You know, um actually psyche knows what I've done
Wait psyche can I ask you a legit question psyche
Wait, I've liked your life or not. Okay. Who's ever doing it? She has already ever done it to your
I've already ever donated to you
Thank you, I don't I don't I don't believe she's person
by he has never ever donated to you.
Oh, she has.
She's referred to client.
I confide.
I see you're a little bit.
So how many clients have I referred to how many people came
over here like donating to you from my fucking pond?
I probably probably a lot of people I can like or dislike.
I will like it when I want.
I fucking support psyche.
You put a penny over there.
Can you donate a dollar right now?
Don't need a dollar. All you all you need a dollar is cause trouble. All you ever do is bring trouble
Don't need a dollar forty
All that blade money you make a bitch you should be able to donate a dollar, couldn't you?
He's making money too summer
But I ain't all no more
What are you doing with this psyche on my tree right now?
Don't worry about what my business is, bitch.
Find out.
It's successful where you have to actually be a fucking maid.
You have to be a maid, so your own business.
Yeah, that's how I own the business, bitch.
I own the business.
You got it right.
I'd rather fucking do hard work than fucking like fucking work.
Hey, why don't you go go and see how much
clean and commercial building is, bitch?
Why don't you do that, bitch?
It's more than what you subject for.
I can promise you that.
She will go with commercial business cleaning up.
You dumb stupid bitch.
I thought you said that you're a maid.
I feel bad for you.
Bitch, I don't feel bad for me at all, bitch,
because I make good money.
She's a good money. You know what?
Like I said, you better Google what commercial building clean is.
Like a hot, like a faxy woman.
Oh, you're gonna fuck with me. That's not so bad for you.
You got AIDS, bitch.
You got AIDS.
Who got AIDS?
You are, bitch.
You got AIDS.
Not your fucking balls.
I feel bad for you.
You got AIDS on your HIV problem.
What the fuck are you to judge?
Why don't you get a job fucking flirty?
Fuck you, bitch.
Your daddy pays all your fucking bills.
Listen, why don't you have your daddy pay your bills?
Are you jealous?
Oopsy you catch. No, he's ashamed of you
Okay guys, well, I'll do okay tonight. It's Thursday night. This is so much psyche. This is I know it's a little bit much
I know but you know we're doing okay JJ. You know, it's like, you know
We have 66 people in chat. We have 66 people in chat. So
Take your funky ass up on out of here, bitch. No, I guess you ain't gonna announce yourself that you gonna leave bitch. You ain't that special
Yeah, I think that blazer waiting for you the streets are like calling your name you are
Guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys
Hey guys, everyone can everyone call me a Bobby here. Bobby's a really talented tarot reader wild wild rave and tarot
Good friend of the show. How are you doing tonight, Bobby? Sup psyche?
Hi, thank you for coming tonight
Trying to catch you live for the past couple days, but I'll be out a little bit. I'm gonna go live cuz I want
Okay, I'll be summer. I'll catch you there. Hey, have you met Bobby be the
To meet you
40 years wait, you're not even 40 years old shut the fucking front
August
Brown don't fall down, baby
I decided I needed a break from life, so I grabbed the bong and thought I'd come and say hi to everybody. What's going down?
It's been a little bit of drama, maybe you can like, you know, always like, you know, have a good night.
Your mic is still dry.
Oh, back here? That's, uh...
I cannot understand you.
It's the zodiac, but it's the major arcana of the tarot at the same time.
Yeah
Yeah, well it starts over here with Ares and it goes all the way around but yeah
Are you related to the zodiac killer? No, I wish no no, I'm not I am related to
Rodolfo Fierro, which was a mass murderer
So there was that
Yeah, I mean, I've been some family history myself. Hey, I was really it's a trial month on allegedly you were all you
You were you were related to Ayatollah Khomeini
Doxing no doxing over here JJ's top this fucking shit. I don't like that
I'm actually really the first measure they did the first or the like the only
Motherfucker back into world. Do you want me to like summon that motherfucker back? Like do you really want me to do that?
Was it that was saying that person look like they had AIDS
Oh, yeah
Who is saying that that was kind of who was saying that was saying that that person had AIDS bummer
Summer was saying flirty diamond has a left summer or left she hasn't she left a while ago
bummer
Hello to her and let her know this is actually what it looks like. So
Summer didn't say that
Christina summer
And sometimes you never know you never know, you know
if you're referring to somebody that it might be afflicted with something and so
I'm going to be careful and not throw it around like you know.
It doesn't bother me when people say that. I mean I do. I've had it since the early 90s.
I don't give a shit. What's up, Gotti? How you doing?
Gotti does do a dark reading of somebody, but not so pleasant outcome.
I think that's the... I don't know a bit, yeah.
There's no such thing as a dark reading. There's just a reading sometimes it's good sometimes it's bad
But it's always a way to find your way through the darkness
Right
because you know
We have this life and we don't know how long this life will last but we one thing is that everyone's that we will die
Right, and so that there's like something later. Yeah, yeah, right sooner or later. And so but then we
What happens after that? Are we are we are we gonna go on are we just gonna like that?
You know, that's that's the end. Is that like, you know, it depends on what religion you are and what your belief system is
I believe in reincarnation. I also believe
Vampires so it's kind of hard to say, you know, I
I believe that if you are fucked up in this life, you'll probably come back to relearn
the lessons you should have learned in this life and given a second chance and you won't
be able to progress until you learn those lessons.
But right
I think a thing a part of that is like, you know everything we do to other people will be done to us whether whether in this life
Or it's mother life
We're gonna experience the same feelings we get
Remind other people or if we love other people will experience more love, you know
It's like it's our choice basically whether to love or or hate
In this life
I have known great joy and great fucked-up it-ness.
I've been a saint in this life and I have been the biggest dick you'll ever meet.
I don't have to worry about it.
I can see it that way.
No, everybody has their own belief.
Well, one of the strangest things that I think was ever brought up to me was everything that makes up the creatures that walk this
It's all the same atomic material that exists in all the planet for millions of years
It's just reassembled in different ways. Yeah, if you believe in a big bang
If you believe in the big bang that started everything that material is everything we are part of everything
Don't know what's gonna happen in the next life. I know that
have deities that I work with that I want to work with them after I pass I
want to keep being a messenger for them so hopefully I'll be able to do that but
I'll say they are maybe underworld deities or at least psychopompous you know deities
They are guides. Yeah, Hecate tends to be considered a darker aspect, but I work with Hermes, who is a lighter aspect, but he also has a cathodic underworld aspect too, so.
Yeah, yeah.
Just like Hecate has a goddess, a light bright goddess aspect as well as the dark.
Almost every single atom in our universe has an electron balance shown and that way I'll have electrons
Every atom has electrons swirling around it. Yeah, and electrons are the magic behind all of our electronic
Every single electronic device, you know my mind
These that we use it's all based on moving electrons
And yet every atom that we see almost every other we see every day
Yeah
What blew my fucking mind growing up was okay, I get the concept of protons and electrons and neutrons
What is the force that keeps them spinning around each other? That's what started my whole path
I wanted to know what bound the universe together
Unfortunately, I picked up a bong in when I was 15, and I love that story right there.
Never found the answer, so.
I love that story.
Yeah.
Okay.
But yeah, then again
You can't you can ponder a electron like no other time when you're maybe it's have just took a hit of the bong
Maybe you can like you know, maybe you can like approach understanding actually what it is. It's hard to put into words, you know
I do a 420 tarot show
Where basically me and my best friend we just get lit we get fucked up and read tarot cards
That is the whole point of the show. We put ourselves in liminal spaces in between.
It's a blast. I really enjoy it.
It sounds a little bit like my show almost every day, you know
I was like I need a bong hit and I'm not just gonna sit here and kick it with friends
So have you had flirty diamonds, Bobby? I'm just meeting everybody. I think the only one
What that before was Jamie's cowboy and yeah
Gotty, I think I'm at Gotti before even Gotti. Okay
What is
Have you met Alexander Alexander Alexander you better behave Alex my friend Bobby
You go get a fucking uterus or keep dreaming with that bullshit
I'm here for the AIDS dude. No, no, I'm here for AIDS guy in the middle. Oh, that's
What dick he sucked did you get in the ass? Like when did you contract AIDS?
You said you're a 90s you've had and you're still looking good
That's okay. You never guessed that in a million years. It's okay. No, I
Started I was a runaway when I was 15
I lived on the streets for a long time, and I did a lot of things.
You told me you were a parent's house or like a group home?
Or you were like, I hate my family, I'm leaving.
My mom was going through her own thing.
She was dealing with her own bullshit and couldn't deal with my bullshit.
So I chose to leave home and handle everything by myself.
What I chose to do was rather than go home,
did things that I shouldn't have done and like we all do because we're hurting
inside and I sold my ass basically I sold drugs I sold my ass I did
whatever I had to do to survive and I'm not ashamed of it
Yeah
Didn't have it. This is you got to remember I'm 55 now. This is 40 years ago
There wasn't the internet there wasn't things available to us to get the help we needed
There wasn't any of that bullshit that we have now
I was alone and I felt when you find out there was no treatment still pretty much
No, no hold on. The party we're going through amazing story. He was 15
You did what you had to do like there was no treatment when you like when you found out oh, I freaked um
How old were you when you find out? I found out in 1993 20 25
30 or 17 I was about it was in my late 20s
uh
27-ish, 26-27, times that they meant nothing, and I found out by accident a friend of mine
went down in Long Beach to get tested at the Gay and Lesbian Center there, and I went with
them and they're like, well, you get tested too, and I soon...
Alright, no worries, and I did and it came back back then it did you didn't get the instant result you get now
You had to wait so the anxiety was there. Yeah, and when I found out I thought my world was over and
is this a before magic Johnson or after cuz I know he let the way like yo you've got a little money and insurance you can live forever
Yeah, this is before magic Johnson. Yeah, this was
before him
So
And the thing is I ran
in in in those days in the 90s I
Ran the club with my friends. I ran the clubs in Orange County in Hollywood
I am the last one of my friends still alive of 20, 30 people, everybody else, either drugs
or disease got them.
I realized in 1997.
I was at the bar, and I was fucked up.
I was tweaking my ass off.
I was drunk, and I was walking back in the bar,
and I looked in the mirror, and I was like,
oh fuck, you're getting older.
And in the gay world, if you're getting older,
you're screwed, and I was like,
I'm not gonna be able to get away with this shit
I'm getting away with right now.
What's up, Pussy?
I made the decision to
get off meth, and I left California because I knew everybody at all the bars, all the bartenders, and we had bar courtesy, I worked in a bar, so you got in free, you got your drinks free, and I knew if I stayed in Cali, I wasn't going to live, so I left town, and I went to...
Ironically El Centro, California, which I didn't know was a gateway for drugs
and
but I stayed clean and
Shortly thereafter met the person. I'm still with we've been together 25 years
So that's an amazing story brother because you look you don't look nowhere near your age
You look 10 years 15 years younger
It's the med would never know in a million years. You have anything so God loves you
Thank you, bro. Appreciate it
I love you, and I'm sorry
The only reason I came up is cuz summer that girl that she like hit something
She was fighting with flirty diamond and she was saying to her you have a
Once we left and then you came up
that's why I came yeah I was like yeah exactly my point and that's my sister that's my sister so
I went and told them like you're some guy up there came up and I was like I'm gonna go up there
and just that's awesome yeah um people say shit like that and they don't realize it's actual people
so I don't make it all I have to do is say hey you know this is what it actually looks like
I'm close to your age like we're in the same bracket in a decade-wise kind of
And when I was young that was like my biggest fear because I had sex unprotected a lot of times now like you know
I'm not gay, but but back then it was such a thing like a it's like
We don't condom condom like you never know and now and every time I had unprotected sex
I would be dying for like a month like oh my god. I might have it
It was like a nightmare
I was I didn't want to live I want then I was trying to kill myself
And that was my choice to do it that way and I regret thinking like that now
But that was the thoughts of a young person who was alone
And that's why I do a lot of work now to try to help people so that they don't feel alone
That's the basis of my tarot practice. I
Try to help people and heal people I do my channel
to help reach people and give them hope.
So you turned it completely around.
Oh, yeah.
You put fear and flipped it on his ass.
Look at you now.
My mom always said you can either fall down
and stay there like a bitch, or you can get up.
Get up, exactly.
Not a lot of people have the courage to get back up.
I
With that disease and all that and look at you now thriving like nothing
I mean, I have my bad days where I can't hear
But they're few and far between and the good days are totally mental. I mean
I'm lucky. I have a good tribe of people around me who care about me and there's always going to be people
Saying shit. I hope you die and fucking faggot and this it doesn't bother me. It used to bother me
Now I do things like that's okay
Now you have a face to go with it and
It tends to have an effect on people more than me being angry does you know
Amazing man. It was really nice to meet you. It's a wonderful meeting you my friend
Here that rips for you. Oh, can you give me a tower reading if you don't mind sure
They grab a deck hold up psyche
Like he's the best
I dig his channel so much. It's an open forum for people. Sometimes it gets a little cray-cray, but I
Still love it. I'm seriously. I've been trying to catch it for the past few days
You came when there's a lot of drama thank you for life when there was no drama
I don't think it ever seems like he's channel where there hasn't been a lot of drama.
That's true. I mean, I appreciate coming up when people said that though, because yeah.
It doesn't bother me when people say shit. I mean, I'm back from the time when gay bashing was a thing.
I also ran with a crowd that you didn't want to try bashing. All right, we weren't no weak-ass punk bitches.
Game marriage or sex in general has really been legal for like what 13 years? I remember being at
Park when I yeah, I
MacArthur Park one time a bunch of people were hanging out after the bar and this is back after bark off poppy's a scandalo
and
It was basically a bunch of
Gay hardcore
bangers
I remember one night somebody just went up and beat somebody over the head with a bottle, a glass bottle of 40.
You know who Eden the Doll is?
Yes.
Like what? I think it was like three years ago she was hanging out with one of her friends and somebody stalked her friend because well she's not possible with her friend.
And yeah, like it was a barn or anything, but yeah, I mean, it's crazy how violence is still fucking being for no reason
Okay, here's what I got for you, bro. You ready? I
Did it already will spread for you. This deals with the energy of the five elements
Earth air fire water spirit in the earth realm you have the Queen of Cubs
You may like people to think you're a bad ass, but your heart is
Golden you take care of the people you love your focus is in protecting what you care about
In the air around we have the strength card in reverse
Now, this card here is telling me that you doubt yourself sometimes.
You're considering changing your career.
You're considering making a huge change in your life right now because you're starting
to think about the future more and more.
problem is you're not exactly sure where to go in the fire realm we have the full card in reverse
I like this one because it looks like homeboy just packing up his shit and making a run for the border
No, he already hate home because right off the bat every day. I give thanks to the four elements
The and actually the fifth earth water wind fire and love is a fifth element
Yep, spirit. So right off the bat. I got goosebumps. Love is the law love
Ties all the elements together
Alistair Crowley with the thought tarot
Love is
Having that full card there that fool is the energy of Uranus your Uranus is the planet of rebellion and upheaval
you want to start
Following a certain thing or doing a certain thing working at a certain place, but you're worried
That shit's gonna go sideways you worried that
It might be a mistake and because of that you're letting fear hold you back in the water realm
You have the chariot, I don't know if these are showing up very well
This is basically a
Bunch of people. Oh, by the way, I'm using the sound the birthday deck
The chariot and reversed says you're at a stand still
It should be forward momentum
Controlling your emotions in a way that allows you the steam you need to move forward, but you're kind of blocked right now
That's further events
With the knight of pentacles
This is the night that falls into the space of spirit
This is the slowest movie night in the deck. He examines everything. It's the energy of Virgo. Virgo is
analyzes
Analyzes and analyzes they overthink the shit out of everything. You're overthinking everything. Don't fucking do that
All right, you're spending too much time thinking that you're at a standstill
All right, and you're gonna miss the gifts that the world has to get to
bring you. I also see that you want to take a trip or travel but for some reason you're being held
back. We have the world card and I pulled that just as a sixth card. Whatever fear
Holding you back. It's time to get over it. The world card carries the energy of Saturn Saturn is the energy
That planet with the ring, right? It's very restrictive
It holds us back
It's time to turn that card from this to this, all right
It's time to throw a little caution to the wind
I will point out that you have the full card and the world card in the same reading
The full card is the beginning of something and the world card is the end of something
But then nice the world card becomes the beginning of something
That's perfection
That's exactly what's happening the end in the beginning. It's like almost a snake shedding its fucking skin
Exactly. A leavers
That's a caterpillar and becoming a butterfly
Exactly what that means bro. It's time to step into the new you because you're thinking shit through too much
Stop thinking start acting. All right
That's what I got for you my friend. Thank you
I think you have a show you said you have really you ask questions about terror or something and
I'd love to be a guest. You just have to track me on a discord Instagram or ask me on the show
Thank you
I would love to know no problem man. It was never mentioned before in my life
Thank you very much, and yeah psyche I would love to get you on my channel hell
I'll hook it up with you right now set a date
Okay, I
Thank you
I think he's married
He's seen a video
I dig a psyche he's his channel is like
How I relax I watch you guys
Channel when I'm doing the dishes or I have it on when I'm cleaning the house and one night. I just decided fuck it
I'm gonna go on and see what happens
Well, this is Alex and this is a hidden camera of Alice and I Alex
What are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over and I've been speeding on the freeway
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm gonna say sir, license registration. I'm gonna pretend it's bad. I'm gonna say step out of the car
And I'm gonna throw you in the bushes in the bushes. I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you in the bushes
Okay. Oh my god. I'm gonna in the in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna make hot car and just fall my way
There's a part two. There's a part two
In the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna make top call and just go my way unless you want to go to jail
I can just can't cuff you ticket to jail or I can fuck you on the side of the highway
It's up to you my man. Okay. Hey guys. Everyone Alice be controversial
But Alice is, he's a sweet guy, he's a sweet guy.
I'm very sweet, I'm a sweetheart, I'm a lollipop, you're gonna lick me like a lollipop.
How many licks does it take to get to the middle of a tootsie pop?
Alex, can I try can I can I lick your tootsie pop Alex? Oh, yeah, baby. Oh my god, okay
I got I love this guy. This good. He's my cutie, buddy. He's my he's my cutie, buddy. Oh
Please you know for me handcuffs. He's a bitch. She never gets old bro. Larry's back to the future
I
Yeah, come up by the way. Oh, yeah, I'll put the link
Yeah, Nick Johnson on Nick Johnson. Hey psyche. What are you doing next Monday the 30 next Monday the 30th?
Okay, sounds good 630. Yeah, the same thing he does every day try to take over
So we can all subscribe. Yeah, and Jamie Jamie. Can you put Bobby wild raven tarot or wild raven tarot?
I love that name. I always did because when I was young that was like the hot guy's name
Like oh can't buy me love like the quarterback. It was always Bobby or like a karate kid
Like there was always a bobby in there. Just like hot like, you know, fuck every little girl's wanting him bobby
I
Bobby a few years ago. It was always Robert, but yeah, I decided to unclean Bobby's
Well, I didn't think my big Bobo once after some girl
Today Bobo. Yeah, you there was a cartoon back in the day
Okay, I don't know. I don't know anymore this
Okay, so as we cash still in the chat
or Bobby by the way, Psyche reads Psalms of the Bible and then he says he wants to
But his and he wants to I think it's called docking he calls it he won't
No, no, shut up everyone listen up to this psyche know something called docking was tongue out about it you put your
Everyone shut the fuck up you do huh?
Well, I didn't and then you put your tippity dick to another dick and then you put your foreskin over
And it's almost like oh
Like Star Wars, when they docked like the USS, the rocket, the ISS, when it docks, it's a docked docked to another dock.
But then he reached the Psalms, where it's docking in Psalms 91.
There's no docking talk, buddy. Like, who was on the stomp?
Like, you know, he's no power, like, party, huh?
Like, I want a dock box. I want a row docking.
Are you serious? I mean, I should have pulled one.
I fucked a million girls. I never heard of docking till today.
Yo, you docking motherfucker. Yo, that's crazy.
Yeah, that's not something I do I don't like I don't like bubblegum. I like
And you were like, yeah, that's when you put your rope and you put your foreskin and you docked the cock
You docked it into that
Where you that after the foreskin is over, then you
What I want to ask you talking your docking experts, how come I have never seen that till today 2025
Because you've never I've seen
I've never seen
Because you never, you never walked into someone on the sidewalk and ran into some other person that had an opposite.
They had forced him and you didn't, or they didn't have forced him and you got it.
That's what happened.
It's a crazy world
Your answer is that's what I'm saying. I thought I'd seen it all though at my age and at these times
That's my point. That's my point exactly. I still learn something you today docking
Holy shit, and it makes sense. Like I can feel shit, but that's all cool like you doff
You know you put it in it's like docking like in outer space
I don't know. I don't know.
We're going to die. We're going to die if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not if not
of the
I just found out what something called yipping yipping is
Oh, what the fuck is that, bro?
Right? Okay, you know those people who dress up in the furry costumes and that when they get in the big
Oh, yeah, they call me
What is it called furries or whatever furries or something furries
Apparently when they're doing the do that's called yipping or yipping or something like that. I
Did not know that I
Just learned that
Well, I can't afford to be a free. I think the costumes cost thousands of dollars. I was like, you know, I don't want all this shit all over me
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No shit.
Get your ass up here, bro. Why are you in the side chat like a little bitch? Get your
Bobby on this panel. Bobby, it's a little crazy around here lately. If I could get a
couple of cards and I'll do some cards for you if it's okay, you know, sure thing. Thank
I don't bother me. I've learned I used to read tarot cards and bars
You learn
Where they mostly drunk a lot of the time yeah drunk checks drunk dudes
Not the bars I went to earth air fire
water spirit and the fifth element or the hidden element
So
What I got for you my friend
is the
Nine of swords in reverse
This is fucked up. It's got a little bunny on a sword
This is saying you're coming out of a traumatic situation, you're coming out of a negative frame of mind and realizing you're not as limited as you thought you were.
You've decided to cut something out of your life, so to speak.
You're trying to put it, replace it with something else though and that's both good and bad.
The next card up is the seven of cups
The seven of cup is is called the wish card
Each one of those cups contains a different path
But a couple of the cups contain poison
So just be cautious of what you're starting up coming up and then your future
In the realm of fire
We have the two of pentacles
This is a card of you being really clever with your money really clever with
Your material things with
Your identity your image your channel this is Capricorn energy
Capricorn deals with our public image. You're a public figure.
I think you're making small tweaks and adjustments here and there with how you want your income to be in the realm of water.
You've got the three of wands in reverse.
This is the energy of Aries. Aries is very go get it. Let's let's get the shit on the road. Unfortunately, you're not really focusing on implementing your changes right away. It's if it happens, it happens.
In the realm of spirit, I think these changes are brought on because we have the two of cups in reverse
This is known as the love card, I think your
Part of you is calling out for something that you're missing and you want to bring that into your channel and into your life
Maybe some things that are a little more spiritual or open discussion doesn't have to be alone motherfucker
you know
it's
Just in that direction where where it goes
You're meant to be doing what you're doing bro because
Your final card the hidden element that ties everything together is called the destiny card
All right, this is you this guy has four arms there. He's working all the elements. He's making it work for him
when you
Decide to do something
Very little can hold you back. I think you surprise yourself a lot of the time
Don't know why I watch your channel and everybody loves you, dude
But that's what I have for you. Just be careful be careful coming up with
What you choose to do?
Think things through okay on the last reading. We had stop overthinking you could use a little more thinking
Okay, okay, that's what I have. What are my cards man?
Yeah, that's hard for you. Yeah
I should have used my wonderland deck. I found the deck. I was telling you about last time
It's this one. Oh
Okay, that's cool. Yeah
Alice video games I play I know I love that game ps4. Yeah
So what I got, huh, right? It's first just a pretty twisted deck. That's all
Yeah, well, I'm actually using my villain's deck. This is the Disney villains and
Starting up we got it. We got a couple Queens
We got the Queen of Swords and the Queen of Wands and you can see if whole I'll put on full screen
We do have like, you know Cinderella's stepmother and we have
you know
The Queen and then her alter ego, right, but you know the Queen's okay
I don't know if these are some powerful women, you know?
Maybe these are your own qualities,
but it seems like these women are women
or these feminine qualities
have been playing a very prevalent part of your life.
Right now, one is very like about mastery of passions.
One is very about mastery of like the tone, right?
Of speech.
Okay.
But then we have this nine of wands. Okay, so this is also this is nine of wands
Looks like you have been like very battle tested and you are you've been through so much
You know you've been a little bit a little bit traumatized
I think that the nine usually has like a little a bandage on their head and they're they have all their defenses up
But also like it looks like in this card. She has this, you know, she's talking to the mirror
And so I think you're very much in touch with yourself able to talk with yourself on a good on a good on a good
Relationship with yourself, and then we have okay. We have the seven of ones. Okay. Okay, so this is her
She's kind of like has her heart over this home right there. There's a pathway. I don't know so this is
I'll read from the book on this last one
The seven of one says
Seven of one suggests you're facing tough competition. If someone's trying to get between you and your goals
Hold your ground. This isn't the time to let down your guard. Keep your defenses up and give it your all
Yeah, it's very similar to I mean this nine of wands and it's even the same queen isn't these two cars
It's like it's like, you know, she's there and she's there
It's like, you know, they're both Sagittarius cards Sagittarius is healing
Yeah
That's in here the healing but it's all but yeah, but it's and it's it's a this one. She's kind of like
Protecting her home this one. She's kind of like has the protection over herself. And so, you know, I
You know, I think yeah, maybe concert on both of those
But yeah, you did get she did come up three times the reading
I don't know if this evil queen from Snow White has any relevance, but she just show up in three of those four cards
I'm gonna need one more card a card of it a card of advice. This is a card of advice how to best move forward
Okay, you got the fool card the fool card best best best move forward with the with the beginner's mind with like a
Innocence with the
Yeah, I think is that him
The message of the fool says it's rocket. Yeah, it does say
As well as Cronk, Yuma's solidly-built henchman Cronk is an enthusiastic and eager to do his best,
however he often blunders his missions by goofing off or getting distracted.
Are the spinach puffs burning?
The fool represents someone who, like Cronk, is excited to embark on a new adventure,
but whose inexperience and naivety sometimes trip them up along the way.
You're on the precipice of an exciting journey.
with a spring in your step and your head held high,
you're ready to pursue a new goal with limitless potential.
The fool advises you to balance your bubbling optimism
with a little common sense.
If you stay level-headed, focus, and double-check
the labels on Yuma's potion bottles,
there's no telling where the new path will take you.
There you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hope you like that.
And as for the two queens.
I work with Hecate and I'm starting to work with Santa Muerte so yeah I see
like the you know the Queen of Wands with Hecate especially and the Queen of
Swords Santa Muerte yeah it's the first thing I thought of yeah
Oh, thank you for that. Oh, you're very welcome. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Gotty. Gotty. Yeah. One of my what are my favorite Scotty
Yeah, well, yeah, that's awesome. And you're such a talented reader. I don't know if
you know
If you have a few more minutes, I don't know if anyone wants to
Ask anything before I know, you know, I know your time is precious. I look forward to the June the 30th or June June
30th
Yeah
I was about to ask you, uh, Mr. Bobby, so we're about to move into a new age, aren't we?
Uh, yes.
We're about to move into a new age.
Yes, it depends.
We're going to talk to, some people call it the age of Horus, uh, the...
Yep.
Yeah, we are heading into a new age, and I don't know if you've noticed a lot of...
people getting in touch with their psychic powers or their spiritual powers or becoming goddess worshipers
the
energy of
The divine feminine is starting to make itself known and when I say divine feminine, I don't necessarily mean
Soft frilly. We're talking warrior fucking goddesses here. We're talking the morrigan
We're talking
Hecate, I I think it's called chriso sandalo po nicotonia
She who stands in hell wearing golden sandals drinking blood. This is the divine feminine coming into power. This is
Strength happened
Interesting right
Jamie I'll throw three cards for you, and then I have to bail that was okay my husband that just came in
Okay, but Jamie's one of the one of the first people I met in here, and she's just so sweet
Yeah, it's awesome
Yeah, I just want to thank you again for the for the readings and just the time and just hanging out being a cool guy sharing your
Experience also, you know, it's like you just share some personal stuff
And I think it might really help a lot of people out there. It's always great when people will share their it's kind of
my
Lot in life what I've chosen to do be a messenger and if I need to open myself up to get that message across and share
Parts of myself, then I do that. You know, I'm not bothered by it
I'm healed from a lot of that trauma already. So
Now up there's one
These he has to go JT, but I'll get you JT. I can probably come back. I don't know how late you're gonna be on
If I can come back later tonight, I will okay
so first card
King of Pentacles second card the hanged man in reverse third card the hermit in reverse
So
Matters of practicality are in play right now.
You're re-evaluating your everything, your home, your job, your identity.
That you hit that yeah
That king of pentacles is
Called the sugar daddy card because he provides everything
I think pressure for you to become something else is forcing these changes
It Matt being able to provide for yourself in a certain way
Um and not have to
Deal with other people's bullshit
The next card I have for you. Well, I forgot to show you
King of pentacles second card for Jamie
Second card we have is the hanged man. Well, it's supposed to look like that. I have tremors in my hands you guys
Sorry, but it's like that
This is you not wanting to see what's right in front of you.
This is the answer.
What is that weird-ass creature?
Which what?
What is that weird electrical creature on that part?
Can you pull that part up again?
Yeah, it's somebody hanging.
They're hanging upside down.
And there's a pool right here up again.
There you go.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
Nice.
I see it, yeah.
The hangman is represented by Neptune. Neptune is the planet of dreams, but it's also the planet of illusions
I think it's at this point you're getting your overcoming some personal illusions and
personal viewpoints
The next I have for you is the hermit card in reverse
This was all my business card for the longest time
The
Hermit card is Virgo energy again, we had this card in another day earlier
This is energy of analyzing everything. This is
It's it's a guy with this leg
Yeah, it's a guy with this leg hanging out as a rope
I got a lot of business out of it, believe me.
Yeah, it does look like a dystopia for sticking by that.
Alright, let's go.
It's a card of not wanting to examine things.
One card of not wanting to get past certain illusions and give up your fantasies or dreams and another card of not wanting to look too close at your life
Unfortunately
It's time to fucking deal with the bullshit and move on
I'm never going to see it any other way now, I hope you're happy.
I'm always going to see the Superstar Sperm now.
Yeah, I think now you're being forced into a position of change and being faced with your own reality,
but that King of Pentacles card says everything's going to turn out right.
it's for the better. So, that's what I have for you. If I come back later, Psyche, I will.
Yeah. Thank you so much. I think it was great having you on. I can look forward to seeing you again
soon. All right, you guys. See you later. See you soon. Yeah. You're a cool guy. You're a cool guy.
So, Bcash, you're the Burger King. Are you the Burger King frog? Oh, yeah. Hello. Do I know you?
Yeah
How do we know sure from a few years
Well, because I've been in your side chat for a little bit, but yeah, okay, okay
Well, I will have been doing I've only been doing the chat for six months and so it's nothing years. Okay, but it's okay
So have you ever been with a guy?
Don't believe people like God.
If you believe God in statements, don't believe God.
Are you one of God's people?
No.
I'm not one of those people.
Why do you all sound alike? Are you a cult?
No, I'm not going to hit people at all.
You're not?
Why do you sound like JT?
Why do you sound like the same as JT?
And also similar to some of the Ziggy.
What?
I said like JT and Ziggy.
God damn.
I guess we're all getting lumped together tonight.
Something that sounds like major too.
She day there is that you and see you see you had a love job. Goddy. This is your person you but you said this guy on the show
I'm a good friend. I'm actually good
The positive people in your channel, and I won't let it down, but I'm a good friend
We haven't known me for years. I haven't been on for years. And so what do you think you think you do?
A little while, but I agree with a lot of the stuff that you say on your panels
Well, if you agree with me, then we're going to be fine.
You're going to be fine.
OK, so spanking, man.
I hope so.
OK, that's not you, Bader.
OK, how am I supposed to know?
JT, we're both three.
Yeah, I don't know.
He, he, I mean, yeah, you're two.
Oh, yeah, so, yeah, you guys are fighting over your position.
Yeah, what's everyone's position?
Who's number one in the chat?
Who's the hero of the chat every chat they start breaking my points whoever's like the most valuable chatter and stuff
They get some points
JT's there
Can't be lying. You might as well shave your head. That's what I did. I shaved my head, but I could grow my hair back
Just like you and I was sitting in your head at your head is shaved. Have you ever been on camera? I
Have yeah
But God if you probably say this
Specimen to be upholding
So have you ever been with a man?
What no fuck no
You came with chicks only
How much you a
165 170 on the good day
You're muscular
You
Are your bodybuilding your bodybuilding no, I don't have to be a bodybuilder just carry fucking
Shanks and little kind of weapons. So no way to fuck with me
That's right. I can't get fucking people you can't jump on me and great me bitch. I'll fuck
CB got great when she was a teenager. That's what she said
I'm not getting great bitch. I'm never getting great. Okay. Okay
That's a real big ass fight, bro.
No, I mean, how do we get the, I was like, I was like,
I think I said, can't give you a hug or something.
And you're like, oh my God, I'm never getting raped.
No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
Gaudi.
Gaudi's like, what the fuck is going on?
Get up here, Gaudi, asshole.
Get the fuck up here.
Stop beating me up here like this.
Is this one of your people, Gaudi?
What's going on?
No, it's nobody's people, but I've seen him before.
He's a big chatter.
He's a big person on panthenia.
Get him off me.
Is he beat macho buff like that boy? No, man. Oh, yeah
God he come on up guys come on I have to go to the store and like you know another 20 minutes
I have another like living line beer. I'm gonna try to like stay up as long as I can
Well, I'm gonna get maybe a couple beers. I'll see if there's anything on sale. I don't know. I
Miss this whole foods and it's like, you know, I already ate a six inch that pepperoni
sub today and then I had
Mike said I had some
Some noodles and then I had what else did they get I got I got a burger. I'm still hungry. I'm like, you know
They're shy. They're shy. They're shy. Yeah, we got his babysitting sister.
Either one of them actually are the best of fucked up part about it. Neither one of them actually is.
I have a little toothpick arms. What are you guys saying about me?
Somebody said toothpick arms. That's horrible. Don't listen to that bullshit.
That's when you have to say fuck you to the opposition. Don't listen to these bitch ass motherfuckers.
Do not listen.
I won't listen, I won't listen.
You gotta put your fucking boots up and say fuck y'all.
Fuck y'all.
So is this your first time on the show?
I don't recognize you from the show.
Are you been on the show before?
No, I haven't.
But I actually, I feel like I'm a good fit for this show.
Yeah
Well, yeah, we all we're all different oh shit, we're all different like we all like a lot of different perspectives there's
Different sexualities different genders
What different people so you like you're the kind of guy they can hang out it can go to a gay bar and not feel weird
Just don't burn your house down, that's all we ask.
Don't burn your motherfucking house down.
Like some people.
You want the wrench, HK?
I don't really have mods right now.
I have Genius Cowboys, it's a few mods.
You're going to try to get, call Crack Baby and BBL?
Okay, but HK, we'll work it out.
Well, if you want to wrench back, we'll work it out.
Uh, let's see. She's not any person, but you don't
Yeah, so he's never had to be cash. You never had one gay experience
Not really other than when I met JT this 10 in GT in the chat
Walked into him and he was offering to suck my balls
I didn't understand why he would do something like that. It was kind of weird
JT is that true?
It kind of has me weirded out.
I didn't want to pursue that or get involved with it,
but this guy in chat, he is a fucking creeper.
He is a creeper.
He's gonna pay out too, but you let him suck your balls.
He let him suck your address because he wants
to secretly sneak up into your house
and suck your balls at night.
How many times did he lick your balls?
How many times?
I can't even say, bro, I wouldn't be doing it in just service if I said it out loud, I'm gonna keep that to myself, but he's a great bro for sure.
Were you like mad at him or did you like, you know, it was okay? What'd you think? You woke up and you saw him do it, you caught him doing it, what'd you do?
You want to make any windows about me, bitch?
Well, let's talk about it, motherfucker.
JT, you want to make any windows?
Let's go.
JT, he says you wanted to lick his balls.
He said you like, or maybe you were doing it.
I told you the whole story.
I've already told you the entire story.
He wanted to lick my balls from the very beginning.
I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I
and you woke him up by licking his balls and he let JT you let him, you need some grooming
and it felt good, yeah, okay.
God you haven't had a fucking woman in decades bro, shut the fuck up bros, you don't even
know what a fucking, you don't even know what a fucking vagina feels like anymore, don't
Class, what were you fucking, you out there?
You know, I bet, I bet, I bet, Gaudi gets tons of vagina.
Nah, Gaudi don't get nothing.
Well, he's been stuck in a wheelchair for years.
He's a fucking paraplegic, you didn't know that about him?
Gaudi's a paraplegic, you didn't know that?
He's like he's like he's like that he's like that guy in the big Lebowski or he's a big Lebowski and like
There's a guy in a wheelchair and like yeah, okay
I don't know. He can't help it. It's like, you know
Vcash is gonna do his first gay experience with me. Do you see me in the Speedos Vcash? You saw you saw that?
No, but I prefer not to.
You prefer not to?
I don't think I was asking too much.
Sorry.
Yeah, because I was almost 9.30.
That's the time I get to my Speedos
and I dance for the guests.
Oh okay well shit go for it bro, I'm not trying to crank yourself bro at all please do you bro
I will, I will, I don't know if I see you as clean so I'm not sure
JT shut up bitch, bro you're fucking as gay as the rest of us, shut up
Did you use
Are they in a gay
Yeah
Guys Gotti
Wild raven the dirty speed of yeah wild raven yeah Gotti this true
Gaudi are you in you and just here gay?
Why would you get so aggressive and try to fight me back you should just laugh at it and just be over it
Your butt heard about it
We should just say that's funny
That's what I did. I don't care about what you bitch. I just laugh at it, but you don't laugh at what I do
No, I didn't is your name on G
God is in a wheelchair. I don't know he's ever David. I don't think he's ever had pussy in his entire life. I don't
Do not believe God has ever been late in his life. There's no evidence of it
Absolutely. No, I got here. You got here. Are you a version of Goddy?
Kosh in Aga Bussie? What is that mean, Aga Bussie?
I'm definitely bisexual. I've got a...
What's Aga Bussie?
Well, it's a wild Ravens. F F R A T E R C E M at gmail.com frauds are sent. Okay. Thank you. What?
Ooga. Ooga shaka. Ooga. Ooga shaka. God, you might be like ran over with the school bus.
All right, are you seeing the whole scope?
I think I like this guy. You're cute. You're cute for a frog.
Can I draw a picture of you?
Okay, VK, I'm gonna draw a picture. I'm gonna put you a full screen for just one minute. I'm just gonna drop you a picture.
You're a really good-looking guy. Wow. These lips.
And
I'm sure okay. Let me see
Laughing at people's trauma
Shut up. You like to a smooth setting
Yeah, you fucking liar. You said he was and you had no part of that
Uh, what a fucking asshole
You know what though, you know what though actually like got a week to hold back on them
I don't feel me
God what the fuck why are we even?
What's your name boy and your name is be cash on?
No, I got to keep talking
What what happens JT? Are you gonna show them?
You're gonna kiss them right JT? You're gonna put the smacker on them
You're gonna put the kiss the kiss of death on them. Okay. It looks just like guys. I think it looks just like it
I think guys ready to see how this looks like you on this be cash. I just your picture
Go for it
Go for it. Yeah, good. You see it. Is that you? I
Like it. Yes, I love it. I
Love that right here. He loves it. Yeah, I got the blowjob lips
I'm gonna show you once. You know, you know, you know, he wants you know, he wants you know, he wants that we're he wants that werewolf cock
the werewolf cock
I'll draw I'll draw his I'll draw it. Hold on. I have to be careful. I have to draw it like appropriately, huh?
Well the main point is I'm not against any of you, I'm not against fucking God, I'm not against JT, I'm not against E-Psych, I'm not against Tiffany, Russ, I'm not against motherfuckers, I don't care, I literally don't give two rats asses about what the fuck goes on in this shit, I don't know, but yeah, let's do that.
W
Okay
That's I can do guys is I vote this look like it. Hold on JT. Tell me
Like that
You never never mind
It looks like a minute to penis
I don't know what that was.
Not very flattering, I'll say that.
I mean, it was just Harry.
Hey, what's up, fairy page?
What's up, girl?
Not nine minutes, I'm going to go grab a...
What was that? That was your...
That was your wiener.
It was all... It was all...
It was all Harry, like a werewolf.
Uncircumcised.
Hi guys
Ingles happy at your picture of jingle. I do v-cache. Who else wants to come up and get a picture drawn tonight?
Show it again, huh?
Yeah, show it again. What was that? That was a funny drawing
How did you come across that drawing?
It's very artistic
Hey Alexa
Like that
Peanuts in the middle of a scribble store. Yes. I mean, the scribbles are the pubic hair. That was a pubic hair
Hey, like
I was to the care
Gears, do you see my picture of God?
Good
I didn't see that, but the people here, I mean Jesus Christ, yeah, look at the camera, look at the screen, that's God here right there.
God, he...
That's him, he has reptilian, his eyes are all reptilian, because he's like a reptilian. Here's easy.
Yeah, he wants to be my friends over there.
Yeah.
You see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see,
you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see,
Okay, yeah, I got it say I see scarlet
Spunky the spunky
This time
Who the fuck is that?
That was time.
Dingle?
You know, Duggy Dog? Oh, there's that. There's Spuggy.
There's Spuggy.
Yeah, see, that's the one I like right there. Keep that one up.
Here are the Crucible Ghosts.
There's Crucible Ghosts.
Jamie's Cowboys
Jay-Daw Jay-Daw
Dougie Doug
It annoys me though
I don't even understand some of my haters, too. Is that a problem that you find yourself in slightly?
Do you not understand some of your haters? Yeah, sometimes I don't understand the haters I have, like why they hate me?
Haters are just people that are usually just jealous
Usually like, oh, well, why that person, why can't this person do that? I can't do this thing
It's like, well, it's like, you know, that's just the world is about it. It's like
Fix the nose. Okay, Jamie. I'm sorry
So I'm gonna be able to do my show because I put hours into it I put a lot of love into it
I was you know ready to start the show. I wanted to do a show so I do my show and so
Where's let's join here you page page you come on page. Is there a particular religion that you believe in boys and other?
Religion you know well now that I studied all of them. I think Tibetan Buddhism is very beautiful. I love like you know, you know, Hindu
Tibetan Buddhism, but I see those parallels with every religion, but
with those religions you can actually do a practice of like, you know chanting mantras and
different things like that were
You can actually transform your mind in the positive way, almost begin to see people as
they do.
You got it everywhere.
Yeah.
It's just how you look at things, you know.
We have a guest.
Let's book a page to this.
Do you have a page?
Where's it left?
I don't know.
Uh-oh.
It won't work.
The camera's out?
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
Just a minute.
Okay.
You can try it.
Ready to go.
Yeah.
She's gonna try to come back
No, I just say prairie dog because prairie says prairie dog. Oh, okay
Who's Emily destiny they pray we're prairie dogs
Are you talking about this thing so anyway, I'm gonna go I'm gonna go to the store, but we'll see page them back
Yeah, I mean
But it's this shit happens
This happens when you're hanging out with these wild ass chatter
these crazy
Shatters like God and fucking
I would name one of them, but I'm not going to name him because he's an asshole, I'm not being a friendly person, so I'm not going to name him.
Do I behave yourself?
Yeah, I think I'm myself. Perfect.
Okay, that's the point wrong.
Hades, you closed the fucking fridge with your fucking ass crack, bro.
Shut the hell up.
What the fuck is Hades talking about?
I closed the fridge in my head, you shithead.
Hades, are you there?
Hades is here?
Is everyone here guys?
Come up on the panel.
We've got such an exciting day.
Who knows the twists and turns we'll experience each day.
Exactly I should throw Katie's in the fucking
Wait, where are you going inside? Are you going to the store right now? Yeah, where did the store?
Okay
My daughter these guys
There's not good food at the play. I mean, I'm always so hungry. I mean I've gotten like two dinners tonight
I mean, I just think but I I didn't miss out like four days of dinner. So it all evens out guys
How's everyone do I must go
Here we go
That sounds good. It's sounds good something like this is um
Yeah, these are crackers. It's like like cheese crackers
Yeah, like a whole bag over 10 bucks
You look at that
I like a guitar
It's gonna show okay. I'll see you on sale
Probably nothing maybe
Okay, we're gonna get more subway. I don't know. How are we guys doing?
Hello, is anybody out there? Is anybody here?
Here's the here's my center
Anybody there
Fresh for those
Let's see what it's today it is Thursday
습득한 이상쎄요
I think I'm probably gonna go get you know, it's that way
She got the 12 inch but
Love the bag of chips into their drink
Oh, no
Not about this is something better better price. Let me see now. Why they've warm
Oh
What doing grocery shopping in the night yeah in the night time
We're critters we do think in the night time
Um, so we're going across there. How are you in that page?
I'm all right. Just having a beer in the smoke.
Thank you, you got it. Hi, Vicky. Hi there.
Oh, gosh, Google GT. Nancy.
Get on there.
What's up, everybody?
Oh, I'm going to drop you.
See.
Oh, those are so good.
I don't know, we're just caught in my hand.
Okay, that went through.
No drama, Vader, no drama tonight.
No, I didn't know for that before I went to work today.
I was going fired up this morning.
No fire today, no problems today.
No, I don't want any more of them,
but like if need be, I suppose I'll fire the stove back up,
you know?
Exactly. Why would you fire it up if you don't have to?
I'm really not normally one to even, I don't get very heated very easily.
There's now two people, two people ever that has bothered me to the point where I like scream like a man.
Hey, did you miss Bobby?
Bobby.
The terror reader.
Oh, like from the Ravens tarot?
I really liked him. I was super cool. We did like I gave him a reading. He gave me a reading like a read-off
Yeah, he was so cool. He was here tonight, but
See I'll get another one of these
Rock stars
Did he like just pop in and catch you live or what did you go up on panel?
Yeah, well he was here for a go. He was here for a little over an hour, did some readings and
We're gonna chat and enjoy
Where do we fix the layout, there we go.
Exactly, why not?
I was going to have a rest in peace service
where I'm interested and chill out earlier today
because I heard he cut off the circulation
in his lower extremities with the painting hose.
What was the tragic event, man?
Okay, he's too weird. Let me know. What are you talking about? You're talking about weird things
I can't hear too well in the subway. See me. Is he behaving himself?
I don't know if he was saying weird things, I just said I'm like
No, he was not saying anything weird, he was fine, why?
Oh, he was fine, okay
I was just gonna tell him
He was being cool
I was gonna tell him
Don't be so terrible
Don't worry about me, bro
He's a frog wearing a gown with like a side-eye smirk, he's good
Okay, you're chance page pages are okay. I'll be your turn
The outlaw steak two times pepper jack pepper at home. I like the outlaw. I like the cheesy garlic steak garlic
aioli
She's here. She saw us. Ooh, garlic steak
Garlic steak is that your favorite
You're a scent for garlic steak. That's how we know psyche. I'm not having
Yeah, I went earlier tonight, and it was it was really good. I don't think I had the hot
We should do you should cook tomorrow instead. Yeah, maybe I will
It would be easier on your tummy, probably, you know what I mean, nice home-cooked meal.
You can make that weird casserole that you wanted to show us.
John Wayne casserole?
Yeah, John Wayne casserole.
Yeah, let's shoot those, yeah, but it's Friday, come on.
Yeah, like cook like a feast
Go get go get like your favorite like eggs. I don't know I don't have much money
You have but like just go buy whatever you love and then make it like he said make it your like your best meal of the week
well, I think the honey pepperoni is a good way to go tonight because
It uh, you know instead of $9. It's like eight dollars, but you're gonna drink and it shifts with it
So you're not really not getting a deal
No, I haven't given them any of the tips. I'm giving the tips the drink and the drink is like a energy drink
No, it's a smell of the day 79 we get a foot long for $3 extra
Maybe I will make it. I'll make it a foot long and then I'll have one for tomorrow
Just fucking getting the subs in you
Yeah, I need anything
I love Subway. What's everybody's go-to sub? Turkey, avocado. Turkey, avocado, spinach,
all that bullshit. Every lettuce thing you can put in that shit. You're a healthy motherfucker,
I like also like I like the turkey breast and I like it on Italian herbs and cheese not toasted with white cheese
I like bacon on it a cucumber lettuce tomato
Yeah, no
It's good all the time. It's good for lunch. It's good for hangovers especially for hangovers with soup
Oh my goodness, you are fancy.
I'm a fucking professional. I'm a professional.
You're fancy.
I'm really redneck actually. I'm actually such a redneck. I'm not very fancy.
You're the one who's-
It doesn't matter. I already believe it. It's too late. I already believe the hype.
Okay, well, that's cool. Then you can call me fancy page. That'll be your thing
Big because is that how you say it? And what's with the frog? What do you look like show yourself? No, I'm just kidding
On a
Probably my eyelash
What's chat's favorite subs when we got down here nobody said anything awesome you guys were like totally invited to this. Oh, yeah
But burger that sounds awesome
Body Colombo what else we've got
uh well that's it fine don't participate pickles and banana peppers actually you
know what steak and cheese here we go holy shit there's quite a few do you know what my other sub
is though sometimes i'll do like a chicken pizza yola and then i'll add like green peppers and
Oh my god, that sounds so tasty like yeah, it's really fucking good, but those that's pretty much my go-tos
See if you did that if you put if you recorded that you would win the chat every single time you did that if you showed that
Taste that's why subway makes it your way not only one way
So weird, why do you guys have to hang out with me?
Okay, how many people are there?
I don't know.
You know, Randy said he doesn't like me and I have a little video explaining why he doesn't like me.
He won't say it.
Who doesn't like me? What?
Randy! He doesn't like me.
I asked him why he doesn't like me.
Is he in the chat?
Let me explain it.
He's a...
He's a dick.
He's a giant dick.
Jummy
Shit, that's probably a little that's probably a little bit
Yeah, let's let's not just keep it out like maybe one insult okay per person. Yeah
Keep it up one insult one insult. Sorry
Is the sandwich maker hot? Dingle?
I love the sound of the sandwich maker. Keep it going.
The sandwich maker hot for sure.
Which clad sleeves side me? I like you. You got clad sleeves.
Thank you. Good night.
What in the world is going on, you guys?
I don't know.
We're all...
We're all alive.
That's what's happening.
I don't know what's happening.
We're all alive.
All of us are alive, people.
All of us are alive, earth.
Destiny was...
Who said that?
Who said real boy?
Oh, dangle?
A real boy!
Where are you?
Oh my god.
You know kids always say movies and they're all sad and shit, they're just like, I just want to go home.
That's how I feel every time I leave my house.
Exactly. And you know what the thing about Vader is?
Vader has never even...
Why is he here?
I don't know what the matter with Vader is, but...
Honestly, dude, I like everyone here, so like, I'm not the person...
I'm not going to talk shit with you, probably, you know?
Yeah, I'm not going to say what's wrong with Vader.
Okay, yeah, sorry
It's all right. Just like, you know, we're grown up so we could probably just not do like whatever if we don't like each other
You don't like each other, but and you know what? I love when we roast each other though
Because that's pretty funny and I could use a laugh right now
Exactly that's why I always say subscribe to all of the friend chats is I always like any roasted myself
I'm not a bug getting roasted, anytime people talk shit on me I laugh my fucking ass off.
Either I mean you're laughing then I'm then when it's not funny. I'll yell but normally I laugh first a bit. Yeah
Yeah
To us than us we already know this shit about ourselves, you know what I mean?
It's like cable. Thanks for pointing out the fuck it obvious for like four years of my whole life that I didn't know this
Exactly you are your you are your own worst enemy nobody
No, a hundred percent, like, just beating the shit out of our self-esteem every day and
third-braining.
You know, like, I wish I would have done this 10 years ago.
Uh, I'm so guilty of that shit, too.
Like, it's ridiculous.
I've made some moves.
Hell, maybe I shouldn't say it like that.
Ziggy, was it you that, uh...
You wanted me to maybe speak to your, was it your sister's husband or your brother-in-law or something?
Did we ever, we didn't ever, was that you? Did we ever move forward with that?
I haven't really seen you since actually, or was that maybe, I don't know, somebody?
Don't kiss I don't kiss that to me. That's really fun. Don't kiss that to me
You got caught
No, we're no kissing no kissing
I'm actually a little taller than four foot, but like you're not you're not really wrong
Do I look sound like a midget?
Or like a kid
Why is it echoing
It was
Geez my other phone was still on so now it's off
It was a little bit more than I thought it would be at the the subway it was cost kind of 15 bucks
I thought it should be like
No, Jingle, I'm 5'2". I'm like 5'2", maybe. My feet are like 6'5".
No, you have it all together. You're the finest shit content with all your shit together.
You have all your things together.
Well, like, I'm not.
So good for you.
Well, thanks. I kind of got some of it together, not all of it.
Nobody's perfect, man. Nobody's perfect. Nobody will ever have it all together. And if you think you do you are fucking wrong
And I got a pepperoni salad with hot honey chipotle chipotle oil vinegar
Subway crunch, that's what you're crunched. You gotta put long and he's got that so maybe we should have some
Is he sounds pretty fucking happy, right? Like you can't argue with that
What fun psyche you have so many things going on that shit
Zoom in on them chips
Those chips
I
But I really like
So do I! Exactly, Terry Page. So do I. I love that. Any time I can get the pizza with the fucking...
Yeah, that's what's up. The little honey hot pepperoni pizza cups or whatever on there? Fuck yeah.
Of course! Yes! I do it every time. Let me get the fucking pizza crust.
And you said I was fancy bougie sub maker one.
I was saying, they're just
making shit up. Yeah, of course.
Destiny and Destiny and Ziggy.
Are you here?
Destiny are you drunk tonight?
Destiny are you drunk?
No, I am not. I can't speak it loud because my girlfriend is asleep.
I know she's upstairs. I'm downstairs in the living room, but I can't speak loud, you know.
Destiny, you sound exotic.
Oh, thank you, it's from Brazil, it's because English is not my native language, you know.
English is boring and lazy anyways, and you sound way sexier.
Canadians are lazy.
We talk lazy.
Oh, thank you, baby.
There you go.
Yeah, what did I just do?
What did I just do?
So I hope you got a $5 foot long.
Is that right?
I
Doesn't matter what where where you came from, you know, where women they came from
Destiny destiny destiny you're you're you're a girlfriend, right? You're you're you're into the you know the taco
Yeah
I'm gonna to Mexico don't confuse
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Listen to me what you Americans learn about Brazil in the in the in the high
Brazil is a very diverse country. You can find anything in the country.
Yeah, yeah. I know that Brazil is the BBL in the Carnival.
It's a big ass in Brazil. I would love to send a big ass woman in Brazil.
Oh my god, I would love to.
No, let me say something. My family, my family comes from Italian family, so I'm very white
and I can tell that Brazil has Italian, German, Portuguese, Spanish, Dutch, Japanese and the
Just like the USA
It's because you guys don't know our history, you know the only thing you see in
In the media, it's it's just the carnival
Okay guys
Yes destiny do you have a destiny do you have a BBL?
Yeah
I'm a white from Italian family. Oh your butt's big enough
Her butt has to be nice, it has to be nice.
You can find the Germans, Italians, you can find Dutch, you can find Japanese, you can
find everything in my country, everything in my country.
And her butt is cute.
It's just terror types, you know
Williams was lying whenever he said like hey, they went over and they saw them and they went
All right, all right, okay.
So I just I just love because uh, you know, let's latinos they
Americans they think that they're different from us
No, the Americans they think they're different from us that they do but they were
originally indigenous land just like Brazil indigenous land that came from
English Portuguese Spanish Dutch
French
Italians people from all over Europe Asian
Africans all over the world, you know
Hey, Bobby's back guys guys Bobby's back. What's up Bobby?
Thank you
Ten times as many slaves as America how funny is that?
No, the thing that you guys think you are superior, it's because you guys have...
No, no, no, the thing that you guys are superior, it's because you have the most powerful country in the world, that's why.
That's not because we think we're superior because we're the best. It makes sense. Okay. It's just like the Rome Empire.
If you start the Rome Empire, they consider the other people superior.
It's just because of that.
back in history you can you can see that you guys what you
Originally, indigenous land.
Okay, okay, let's change the topic.
We're going back to maybe talking about some terror or...
Okay, okay, alright, alright, alright.
No, no, no, it was interesting.
It's interesting, you know, it's interesting history of Brazil and stuff, but let's...
Alright, alright, alright, baby, alright, baby, but I am a white...
from Italian family, okay? Okay, okay. So
It doesn't matter if it were black, it doesn't matter if it were black, you know, it doesn't matter if it were black.
Yes, yes, this is African family. Just hang out, just hang out, enjoy the conversation. We don't have to get too heavy into it.
So Bobby, how are you, Bobby? You're back, you're back.
Hey, yeah, I'm back. I saw Paige was on. I had to come back and say hi.
Oh, cool.
I
Had I'm a caretaker for my own and I had to go make sure everything was cool
I just like to hear to the girls late to the girls boys, you know
I like you women. I will compress that I like you women. I was born this way. I like you women
No, I'm a I'm a female. I'm a female. You were looking for I am I am a female lesbian lipstick
I really like women and if I see a beautiful woman it doesn't matter her voice you know
I will compliment her okay well you know what you know there's I know a woman named 30 diamonds
I want to hook you guys up and so you know just just just hold off I'll hook you guys up okay so
Are you paid just you play a matchmaker motherfucker? I know I'm Mr. Cupid tonight. You'll love you'll also be done
No, here we go. Look, what are we looking at? Look at Paige. Here we go, Paige.
Here.
Hi, Paige.
Oh, Paige. Paige is sexy. Paige is...
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, she is.
I can't watch the page. I'm sorry.
No, I have to leave.
Paige, you are hot, girl.
Paige, you're continuing with the hat.
No, I wore it at work.
Like, it's almost...
And you wore it here and...
I know you wore it for me.
It's okay.
Well, I usually wear a hat, and I wear a hat that I can put my head outside.
I had to yell in the background, sorry, hang on.
Oh my goodness, she's so cute! She's so cute!
Hey
Everybody likes you men the women men the women there
Hi guys, we're all beautiful people.
All beautiful women there on the panel.
That's me, beautiful woman.
Yes, beautiful woman.
That's right, I love American women, British women, it doesn't matter what they're from, women are beautiful, whatever they're from, you know.
Brazilian mothers, they are very famous in America, in the US, you know.
Okay, we'll come to calm down or you know, and then we got some hotties here
We're you know, we're all gonna keep professional
Hey your single, baby
She got so mad she left.
Oh, you are so lucky.
You are so lucky.
What can I do?
I'm a cookie maker, you know?
You both are so beautiful. You both are so beautiful, you know
Everyone's very flat everyone's very flattered. Thank you destiny, but let's let's let's let's like, you know
We get it. We get it. We're all beautiful people here, right?
I
Spunky you you look so beautiful
Page you looks you guys are so so so beautiful
No
What about me I mean me and a Bobby or chop liver, right?
I don't I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I need to get my speed off my legs right now.
I'm not attracted to men. I haven't been to men. I haven't been to men before, but I am not attracted
to men. I like women. This is just my nature, you know. Okay. Okay. Well, you know, I feel kind
of left out. You're just saying all these nice things about Spunky and Paige and you can say one
Here, I'll say something hot. Oh, you look like sexy Jesus. How about oh my gosh?
Jesus is like totally hot on the cross he did
Abs his abs were great. It's abs of abs, dude. Yeah
Sorry about my dog
the cats go wild and the dogs are mad that the cats are running around so everyone's going nuts
yeah Spencer well there's life with animals I got here's here you guys haven't seen the nor
here's my little baby the nor I don't know if you know the nor but I mean and and when I love it
when they speak English because I was I was learning English on my own and I'm still learning
you know, so there's some things I don't really understand.
It shows.
Yeah.
Well, you can see my accent, you know.
There's some things I can't understand.
Oh, your pronunciation isn't really the problem here now, sweetheart.
Yes.
Yes, because it's not my native language, you know, and I'm still learning, I'm still learning, but I found a really nice dog to me.
Oh, that's so cute, that's a dog, that's so cute.
She's so cute.
How do you make Christina's dog?
Christina has a dog named Fawzi.
He looks very similar.
She has a full size one.
He's got like 18 pounds.
She's tiny.
Oh, she's adorable.
She's a real lover.
She's annoying though because she only wants to be held
and snuggled all the time.
So if you're not doing it, she just sits there and licks you.
Yeah.
Demon do you want to come up? I don't know where we're three diamonds been our dingles
You want to come up Justin?
Justin boils in the chat anybody can come say hi on the panel. We have a Bobby
Wild raven tarot. We have spunky. We have
Boyle guy in the chat room. I don't know. He's a see some weird guy that comes to my chat sometimes
I know he's really odd. He says some weird stuff doesn't he?
Yeah
He makes me he makes me. I'm comfortable
Page as soon as you turn your head page ran out the door she was
I scared her out she was not ready for a lesbian relationship, but
Keep trying keep trying. No, no, no, no, no, man. If I if I compliment or what I women
Thank you, I know that
I would love one body.
Can I ask you what your sign is before we start? Pisces.
There's one card I'm expecting to see, the High Priestess, if she shows up I wouldn't be surprised.
You're giving up very high priestess vibes to me very strong
feminine spiritual energy
There
There's never gas in my car and my phone's never charged
Hey page, how are you?
Good, how are you? So here's what I got for you spunky. Remember I said I was expecting the high priestess card to show up
Yes, sir
Well, the high priestess is ruled by the moon. This is the moon card very similar energy to the high priestess
This is telling me that you are no you are reading
Destiny destiny, I don't want to kick you out of the room. We're doing a reading just quiet till the end of the reading, please
Thank you so much
The moon card falls into the earth realm. This is a card of spirituality
It's a card of feminine strength right now. You're not feeling your full feminine strength. You're not
Leaning into your full power right now something is
stop being you. You've reached a point in your development where you don't want to
look deep within anymore. You don't want to look in certain areas.
Whoa, tough shit, bitch. It's time to look, okay? The universe is telling... Yes, and I
talked this way to my clients in professional readings, and they still have a path.
It's time for you to handle your shit, all right? It's time for you to look in the places you don't
In the airspace
We have the page of swords in reverse. It should be like this
When it's like this, it's new beginnings for you. It is
Starting to see things in a new way
leaning into new ideas
When it's reversed though
Your development is kind of something which means you're having trouble with getting past a very specific thought
Something is freaking prick in you. You're having trouble getting past it. It's just
Like nails on a fucking chalkboard for you
In the fire realm
So, in the fire round, we've
got the Ten of Pentacles in
reverse. So, this is the Ten of
Pentacles. This is the Ten of
Pentacles in reverse. This is
the legacy card. This is telling
me you're worried about family
matters. Um, definitely.
I don't know if you're scared of something ending or a change coming, but tins are a symbol of change.
They're the end of a cycle.
This is you refusing to accept that cycle, refusing to accept what's happening around you.
I can't tell you if you're right or wrong, I can only tell you that your mind is set on your way of thinking.
I'm going to tell you this. Your way of thinking will lead earth, air, fire, water. In the water realm, we have the Nine of Pentacles.
So this is a card of material wealth. It's abundance.
You can make anything work, apparently. The trick is you need to take the harder road all the time.
Sometimes you have to then to save yourself a few cuts and bruises if you know you're gonna end up in the same white place
anyway
The heart is a fight mode. Yeah, I know that too. I get telling my friends that
Adventure I
agree
My friends tell me you're gonna run into a brick wall and
Later on they'll see me and I'll make this symbol, you know pushing my nose to the side. I
Do it and I did it anyway. Yeah, you're gonna do what you're gonna do
But do you need to have do you have to that's the question. All right
The next card up for you is the ace of pentacles in reverse. This is telling me that
Different employment might be coming your way
Are you thinking about changing your job not at all
Okay, well, this is new money
new
The aces carry the energy of Capricorn forests in Virgo. So anything tangible, anything new, anything, I am building a new house. So
That is definitely it. This is that carries the energy of all the earth signs your
house is your identity with
Capricorn, it is what you value
with Taurus, and it is where
your thoughts lie with Burko.
So, I understand now why that
ACE is there is that it's just
one of those Earth cards.
I think the other thing too is
the house that I'm leaving, I
don't really want to leave, but
there is family growing and I
have to in order to make
I don't think the journey is going to be as smooth for you.
Have you been having some issues getting this rolling
in the way you want?
Well, it's not the house building that's the issues.
It's the people that are going to be living together,
not getting along.
Well, know that the ace is the beginning.
Okay.
It falls into the spirit realm and this
This is definitely a positive sign for you
what worries me is the next card the hidden element and
At first it concerned me until I thought about it, this is the death card um, but it came out reversed so
At first, I thought it was a serious change, but no, it carries the energy of Scorpio.
Scorpio is defensive about the home.
When you said you didn't want to give up your current home, Scorpio is protective.
It's a fixed water sign. They're very defensive about what they care about and what they love.
This is you being forced to give that up.
You're home is wherever you the fuck you are so
Don't worry about anything just to bite the happy spirits and good memories to go with you
All right
But you're on a new adventure that ace in the death card right next to each other
If you can get past the feeling of loss you're off on a brand new road so
All right, so what I got for you boo. Thank you. Thank you
All your dog is so adorable
She's so she's so sweet, but she's so stupid too. Like she's just like she's all love like what's name
Miley
Hi Miley
It's a little little fluffy curly curly. I know her little eyes. I could trim them every day and they're still covered up
Justin thought that was a great reading
Yeah
Kisses kisses kisses kisses. What are you doing? No
Oh
Say hi, she's like to who?
To everyone. Yeah, look, there's people on there. Yeah, you see them
Like isn't that the dumbest face
It's so cute, but it's so stupid like there's like three brain cells fighting each other for their lives in there
He looks like what a baked bean. Yeah, I
Know page page was looking forward to talking to Bobby tonight. I saw page I wanted
Yeah, you did. Oh good
Yeah, hello like a polite girl
Destiny. It's okay. That's it. It was just during the reading. You can talk about it. Don't worry about it. It doesn't you're fine now
Never you want to talk. I didn't mean to I didn't mean to shut you up. I was just you get you can unmute yourself
Destiny that you've done you all I can
Is an implant no
You're here, but destiny can you hear me?
Vicky and Hannah, you need to kind of maybe not be so ignorant to each other in the chat.
You're going to be saying something on it.
Yes, I can't.
I just want to know how old our pagey.
Let's see if you can, why don't we play the guest in game, I'm just kidding, I'm 34.
He's 34.
Yeah.
Like good that good destiny. No, you you you are older than me, okay
Oh my god, I just felt like my fucking bagel.
Oh my god.
Because it's like a mason jar and I just went and put my hand around it and I wasn't looking
and I wanted to go grab my beer but I grabbed my...
No, no, I was mistaken.
I was mistaken.
I am older than you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, okay.
It's an easy mistake.
Yes.
How old are you, Destiny?
You're you're 60 years old that's me
I'm a
Okay
You're still younger than page you're still younger than page page is 34 the age of Jesus the age of Jesus
There Jesus your Jesus Jesus was 33
Yeah
Right
Yeah, John Wayne Gacy at 33 victims. I mean 33 is just
Yeah, what's up page I said, I wonder what 34 means. Don't be not good because this is the worst fucking year my entire life
Well, three four three plus four seven seven is a chariot. Maybe moving forward with your plans
Our body resets itself every seven years, every seven years we're a new person, so you're a new person.
I'm a bit sorry because English is not my native language and sometimes I mistake, you know.
That's okay.
I make mistakes.
It's okay. Everyone makes a mistake. Everyone makes mistakes. You know that
You're welcome
Thank you
Okay, well, you're not just remember the first time you came myself
itself
You be it regenerate you every seven years our cells
Right. We're almost in a different body. Yeah. We're almost in a different body.
I am a Christian myself. I'm a Christian myself. I will buddhize it. But if you want
to bring some cars for me, you can go ahead. Oh, can I, can I please? Hold on one second.
You know, I'll give you three cars, my dear.
Destiny is going to be ready for you.
Listen to me.
You know, you know that beauty can kill someone.
Okay.
Now
Destiny just listen just listen to this and here's your cards destiny, okay?
Now you gotta listen real close. The first one for you is called the first house
This is the body. This is saying you may be having some issues with your health coming up
Make sure you keep an eye on
Your diet especially your
cholesterol, that's the word I'm looking for. All right, we don't want anything clogging up those arteries.
But the third house is the next card.
This is
messages. Pay attention when people are trying to give you messages over the next month.
You're going to hear something possibly about
I don't want to say something that was hidden from you, but something that was hidden from you, basically.
The truth is going to be coming out on something.
And the third card I have for you is a card called the North Node. This is your life's purpose, alright?
This is saying you're supposed to be doing something, you're starting to do it, you've been working towards it.
Don't give up on your your goals now. Yeah, I know that it may seem
Like you can put it down and pick it up later
That won't happen. If you put something down right now, you're not gonna pick it back up. All right, so
Follow your dreams of what you you're trying to accomplish right now and do not stop
That is what I have for you
Oh, thank you.
You like that. If we like that, uh, Destiny,
you know. No, I
appreciate it. I appreciate it. Yes.
You are great. Great. How's everyone doing in chat tonight? Everyone getting along? Are people fighting? What's going on?
They're good now. They're good now.
Yeah, it's straightened around, I think.
Okay, that's neat. Savvy Joe.
Oh
Hey, we got rusty in the chat shout out rusty. I see rusty. Hey spunky Hades
Leia Justin
Vicky platform views guys who's in first place, you know, we have a new point system
There's like a the top chatters. Tell me who's in first place. I want to know
No card is gonna tell me my life purpose. Well, maybe not Hades
But you know what that if your life purpose is for you to decide your life is the cards aren't gonna tell you
I'm not telling you your life purpose. It's telling you to follow your life's purpose
It's saying that if you don't follow your life's purpose, you're going to regret it
Hey guys, don't tell you what the fuck to do. They're just cards
Yeah, I mean
Of what you're know on the inside is clarification for your intuition that connects the cards connect with you
It's your story
Hey, you shut up
You look good
Shut up
We just took our spot. I'm Canadian. I will fight.
Destiny, I know you're trying to eat me.
Okay, okay. She's trying to say you're cute, Paige.
Stop saying shit when I'm trying to take a drink of water.
Okay, okay. Bobby can't stop laughing.
Hey, Destiny. Paige is not interested right now.
Page is uh, you know in her Herman and neither is Bobby neither
I don't I just want to compliment that I just I just want to compliment her
How about Sponky Sponky has a boyfriend and be cat be cash
I want to date next and so you can't you have to stop hitting on the whole chat. Okay
Oh man my grinders all the way over there. I think that was a yes. Okay. Hey guys
How are you doing shit? Okay the grinders all the way over there. Hey, I've got a I got a I got a vape right here someplace
Where's my vape? Oh
I do
You're a really good vape. Oh, they already open this one a shit. If I open this one over here
You
You want to like do you want to rip me up a little a little message or what I don't trust many people to read my cards like
Scythe can you and like Bita can
Absolutely, let me crush this up
Are you straight
One hundred percent. I'm straight as a fucking arrow. Yeah
Baby girl
Okay, guys, you know what we're all
Buds is it's okay. I think hey, hey, hey, this is flat. I think she's flattered right you're flat
I'm flattered. Thank you. You're beautiful, too. I can't see you, but I can read your energy and I can see your soul
So I think you're beautiful
I'm smoking I'm not drinking well, I'm drinking
Let's smoke a pot to tell that
I'm not going to let you choose the deck. I'm going to use okay, so I need you to tell me left or right left
Alright, one or two. One. One of my favorites, the Crow Tarot. I have that. I have the Crow Tarot.
That's the real thing
Like real guys like
All right, I'm gonna need you to use while I do this I need to concentrate
Yeah, I was supposed to interview her and because of that
I'm in Arizona where our time doesn't change the time got fucked up and
That interview never happened, and that was just for
Devastated one of my heroes man. This deck is awesome. I can meet my idol. I did
all right, so I
Elemental spread card one in the air. We have Queen of Swords
Or I'm sorry earth
We have Queen of Swords in air. We have the seven of swords
In fire we have the wheel of fortune in water
We have the reverse
Seven of swords and in spirit we have the nine
I'm sorry the seven of wands reverse and then the
nine of wands reverse
Hey
So, in the upper half, this is showing with the air having that seven of swords there.
feeling like you can't fly properly.
This is coming from your circle. There may be pressure on you in a certain way to
go under direction, you're not ready to go in to heal certain things within you that you're not ready to heal.
And I say that because on the next tier down,
And we have the seven of wands reverse and the nine of wands reverse.
You're healing yourself and you're doing.
What you have to do, but you're doing it at your pace. So you can basically tell everyone around you
That's trying to get you to do things or think a certain way or be a certain way. Tell them to go fuck themselves. All right
Your meant to take your life in the way you want it I
Think your spirituality healing
It's a gift to the world that you need to lead into I
think that
The mundane world has an effect on us it always does
but
You're one of those people who are able to rise above it and spread light and I love that energy
I'm back down to that Queen of Swords in the earth realm
This is
Sovereignty at its best. This is the bitch who wields the sword. She will cut you or she will cut you off either way. She's not moving.
This is you having to stand your ground on what you believe in.
We have the Wheel of Fortune
Now normally that's an iffy thing
But if I'm reading this correctly it's
Incredibly powerful thing the Wheel of Fortune is ruled by Jupiter. This is growth and abundance
But this is an inner
Spiritual growth that you weren't
Friends how you something similar like this before?
You're taking your spirit or a step deeper then
Other people can go or other people will understand
so
What I want to say to you is, hold on, I get that.
The car that links everything together
is the Eight of Cups, but it's in reverse.
This is telling me not only are you able to walk away
from something, but you're walking into something
more positive.
You're walking into a different view.
And you take everything, the advice is take everything at your own pace, all right.
This is a card of Pisces.
Pisces is not only incredibly spiritual and psychic.
But it's the house of endings. All right, so the old you is pretty much ending in you
I you are being reborn. You're going through a spiritual repress. So
Yeah
And that's what I have for you. Thank you
Wonderful
Bobby, I'm gonna hit you up for like a personal though like mean you one-on-one. I think at some point here
Absolutely on the house. I'll give you an hour on the house seat. Oh my gosh
Well, and if you want one for me, you know, I'm always down to do that. I would I would dig on that
Yeah, I have a lot of people in the community, but I'm very picky about
Who I let my energy touch, you know, okay? Bye. Bye. Just me it was fun. I was
With somebody fucking aggressively mouth-breathing the whole time
Was that you be cashed
I'm you know, but she can figure out unmute herself, but I was gonna unmute her. She was just being loud during me
I just wanted to
Let you guys get his vibe, and I think that was that would have been a dude coming at you like that
I'll hell of room for this
Well, you know destiny dinner destiny's a little bit aggressive, but you know, I don't think it's a bad person
Yeah
What's interesting you guys having a good time 20
Very interesting
Instraging grace is to say instraging instead of interesting and I know I can't be it like a normal ever again
and
She used to say ambience and commercial it's a commercial I
Used to have a problem with the word penguin
It was
Coming out. What was it hanging hanging or something like that? Yeah, it came out really weird
Apparently I wish I didn't have much cause to say it so we didn't fucking
You're just figure a life. Oh, you're just trying to figure out how to fucking speak, you know what I mean?
You can't help that I say kitchen. I guess it's a chicken
You heard a chime I heard a chime
That was mine
After reading I do it normally ice. Yeah
Normally, I knew when I do that
Lovely
rituals
So but but Bobby you're so I know you're into the Lima it sounds like you've said something you said the Alistair Crowley a little bit
I'm not into the lemak, but I do read with a fox arrow
Yeah, you were to talk to her and you know he made that was like lady. What's the name lady lady?
Yeah, he made a Harris a pretty hair. Yeah, it's all of a sudden free to call it
If you want to do the deck she had to trick him into it
Yeah, she hired him for two bucks a week to to help her
Oh
My girl
Cool story. Yeah, I know you know
No, I have to get them done. They're frickin brutal. I have to go get them done next week
But I haven't had a day off. They're like red and black and are they cool
Pretty three weeks over do you aren't they? Yeah, they're both. Yeah, they are. I have a
Guess what I used to do for 14 years
Nails nails I did nails for 14 years
Did you do nails for 14 years? Well, can you tell it to me?
That's why I was like, that's a three-week till right there, doesn't it?
You know it is. You fucking know it is.
You know what? Can you get into the crystal ball? Can I just, can you come here and can you do them for me please?
Right?
It's awful man. I may not do that for a living anymore
But when I go to the grocery store and I see but see somebody's jacked up claws
It just breaks my soul every time. You're like honey. Why you not love yourself, honey?
Angela, Angela Johnson
We get you for rent. Yeah
She was so I got I did I didn't buy like a like a 30-piece nail care kit today. Oh, yeah, here's my subway
Looks good, huh? I bought a 30-piece nail care kid has all the scrapers and the clippers and everything I need
So my nails will look better. I got on Timu. I got
People laugh when I tell them I did nails, but you know what I got 50 bucks a set
And then I was 60 bucks a set and I started off with 20 bucks a bill and I ended up at 35
for a bill so
That was 35 bucks an hour
guaranteed Bobby you're never believe this I literally have a nail table and
like three grand worth of nail shit in there that I've never like I don't
you fucking listen I took the nail course because I'm an artist right so
took the nail course and I was like oh I'll just do my own nails at home it'll
be such a great plan la la la la okay guess what guys I'm a fucking ambidextrous
only got one dominant hand one hand looks right
Frank in hand. It's terrible. So it's like fuck this and the whole point of going to get your nails done is for like someone else to do it
Okay, let's be real and just I'm kind of a perfectionist so and I would take so long
It wasn't the nails. I like to do it was the art. Do you know what I mean?
Yeah, so I'd actually use your nails would be work works of art
So it's just I don't know it just became a thing and then I started to make jewelry
I
Don't want to talk about where they change anymore
I just want to know Peggy, Peggy, where are you from?
Canada
I just want to know Peggy, where are you from, baby?
Oh, I hope so much ingust.
I need a bongrit.
Peggy, I have a beautiful girlfriend.
I have a beautiful, I'm a lesbian.
I have a beautiful girlfriend.
I'm glad you told me I was never going to.
Clutch the pearls, what?
I just, I just want to know where you, where are you from?
Far, far away land.
Way over the rainbow.
Page, page, page is like pages, pages are anonymous.
I'm actually a 93-year-old woman. I only have a few years.
Baby, baby, baby, you don't need any of me. We're here.
You are so beautiful you don't need any me
You are so sweet
You don't need you don't need any me right here. I have a beautiful girlfriend
She's blonde. She has green arse. Green arse.
She has a green arse. What?
But arse is green. She needs to get that checked out, love.
I better go to the doctor and get that checked out with that green arse.
That's not a good sign. I don't want to talk about religion anymore.
No, no, it's not religion. It's not religion.
I already have one of those. I just want the whole page to be.
Destiny, what do you have to say to Paige?
Destiny, say to Paige. Say it to her right now. It's your chance. Let's hear it.
I just want to say that she's really beautiful. She's really sweet, you know, she deserves the best
She doesn't need anything
Thank you so much
Oh my gosh
She doesn't means any guys from here, you know, because
Most beautiful girl
Okay, that's me. Thank you so much. What a great here. I love you
Okay, well
Hey, yeah, it's actually a 92 year old dude named Alvin. Yeah, I was using a filter
So this is a real person see you pinched my little cheeks
Man you what do I go?
I'ma tell me. I'ma tell me. I'm from Brazil. I'm from Brazil, you know, I am I trying to learn English
you know
And I can tell that I love, I love a Brazilian, I love Brazilian girls, I love Brazilian girls, I love American girls, I love girls from all over the world.
I love women, I love women. I am a fucking husband.
i am a fucking lesbian i'm a female lipstick lesbian and i confess i confess
me too i'm i'm not i'm just very glitch i don't care what what you guys think i am a
Lipstick lesbian. I love the women. Women are so beautiful, so sweet.
Did you know that? Well, you probably don't know this life between sister.
I
Haven't been with the men before
My twin sister the lesbian is allergic to cats and I'm a gay dude who's allergic to nuts
So nuts will kill me and pussy makes her break out
You're so beautiful, baby girl
just I don't know I don't know how old you are but just go to college just go
make your life don't get a boyfriend right now you're only you're so young
Older than we would think, I guess.
You're almost 13. You're almost 13.
Yeah, my daughter.
She's almost 13.
No, it doesn't.
But it doesn't matter.
Just go to college.
Just just make it your life.
Don't depend on your man.
Yeah, you're making an assumption that she's never been to college. Why do you think she's never been to college?
Do I look like I never went to college?
Yeah, you're assuming that she doesn't have an education.
Man, even in my country, we live in the second world.
Just go to college to make your life don't depend on men.
leave your life. I agree on that.
I'm going to keep doing it. I'm going to point in my life right now where I have had to, had no choice to make some changes.
And so I'm going through a lot and I'm making those changes and school is going to come next year, so I'm already doing it.
I'm going back, I'm going back to school because I did go to I did go to nursing school and I also did take a bit of like, you know, English major. I've done some things with my life.
If I have done.
It would be that I didn't go to nursing school. I've wanted to be a nurse.
No.
Guys dust dog dust dog you are you didn't get awarded a membership. I think I I think I was one of the ones that
Ordered your membership. We've had over 20 memberships awarded in the past couple of days
I want to say thank you guys for for awarding the memberships. I purchase about us, too
We don't leave in the 90th century anymore
Women can be free. They can be they can do be whatever they want to
What a beautiful message, I mean, that's a beautiful message women can do what they want to do. Yeah, we already know
Hard just she's a beautiful girl
She has a life ahead of her head.
Oh, she does.
She has.
Yeah.
We know.
Pages, pages, pages.
We know because I know.
Because I know what, what's happening.
I know what a page first is.
This is awesome, everyone loves Paige, everyone loves one person that's in love with you.
Destiny, you want to play Trubia?
Let's just change the subject for a little bit, Kay.
Kay, thank you, love.
Let's do that.
I really love, like, I love, I love, I love you, thank you so much for the beautiful
kind words, but let's, let's move on.
Hey, Scytheys, look at this strength card from my Alice deck.
Are you gonna be Alice day, too?
Shadows oh, yeah, that's awesome
I love that I love that
Please
Okay. Thank you. Thank you so much. Thank you so much, Destiny. That was wonderful having me in the show
Okay. Yeah. Thank you. That was awesome. That was awesome Bobby. I love it. I love it
Let's try because you know, I get the strength card a lot and I'm also my birthday is one seven
so that's eight and
Is the strength card?
Yeah, it was also the justice card
Depending on which system you so now one says it's important
And also, I have a north node in Leo.
My north node is Leo.
And so I really do with it, yeah, flying.
Hell, yeah.
Oh, South Node Aquarius.
And Aquarius South Node can be kind of a lever.
You good good. We're good. We're good. Okay. We're all good. We're all good. Oh, yeah, everything everyone's here
Listen to me listen to me
Living in the second the world, okay
My my country has a lot. We love you. Oh, that's me love and now, you know
She doesn't even know it's okay
Hey you you guys look how you page in and bobby kind of look alike with the glasses
You know what when as the nail tech I had my glasses down like that all like all the time
Yeah, well because
You're looking down and so they just live
And I got a big nose so they had a long way to slide
Yeah
Because you said you were gonna pull for me. Oh, I know but I just I don't I didn't have a moment to
I know I think we have a moment
Destiny's backstage and she's eating the doughnuts. She's like just eating some doughnuts backstage. Go ahead destiny
You know you can come back when you're
More calm down after after the reading. I don't I want the read
Here I'll get pagey. You're on you're on full you're on full
No, no, no, we're all here
See those people that getting glasses
Well, it's not a fashion show I fucking see
Right, yeah, it's not for like it's not aesthetic. It's very annoying to have to wear
But I have three
Yeah, just for reading and honestly and driving and like other like things that I have to see like little stuff
I don't know. They have to pay like life
Look, I just need them to see sometimes. Okay, you guys get off my back
Get off my job
Oh my god, oh my goodness
Maybe one more. This is intense. The sea serpent keeps coming out for you. I've spotted it like six times now, so it's kind of like hard for me to ignore.
And that card is incredibly cool in here.
This is very precious to me.
Okay, that makes sense.
We're going to read that one, but I also want you to do the intuition thing. Okay, ready?
This is the only deck I do this with but I think it'd be fun because I didn't get to
do it with you last time and it's kind of like my initiation deck in a way.
Does that make sense?
Yes.
Okay.
So I'm going to let you say when as if you're putting parmesan on your pasta.
You got it.
Ooh, clump.
When?
Ooh.
You sassy bugger.
What was that shit?
Alright, ready?
We're going to try it one more time.
Here we go again.
When?
Yeah.
Top, bottom, or middle.
Okay, hold on.
Let me explain this first.
So, it's the animal spirit deck.
Have you ever familiarized yourself with this one?
I've seen it. I haven't used it.
Okay, so and it's like just kind of there's like the odd like there's like reptiles and like, you know, like
Manhole, there's all kinds of animals and like there's some bugs in there
And then there's like a couple like mythical things as well
So just I want you to do your you know how to you know how to fucking play the game. Yeah, okay
So top bottom or top bottom or middle?
Okay, and what do you think it is you don't have to be specific, but you can be if you'd like to be
What animal? Yeah. Or what being? What creature? What thing? What thing it is?
What thing?
You're thinking about way too hard. You already know that. You should have thought the first thing that came to your mind.
Beaver is the first thing that came to my mind.
Is it beaver in this set?
Well, it's building something. It was the concept that came to mind. So spider, beaver.
ants, bees, anything like that, building energy.
Okay, that's fair.
And split.
Oh shit, that's not the middle.
There we go.
We actually got this stingray.
It's interesting, but let me just check the talk. Let me I'm nosey. I'm gonna just see what's on the top
You're a serious thing like a bee, right?
I don't know. I think you die if you get stung by one. Isn't that how Steve Irwin died?
Yeah, that's how he died. He got stuck in the heart. He got stuck in the heart. Yeah. How, how in fact, that's
I'm sorry. I, I, I think that's sad, but your ass never should have been touching his being right that close
You shouldn't put your anything there or that something that close.
Yeah.
Ever.
The panic.
Panic.
Okay.
I just don't think certain major shows need to be getting all like that of animals.
The beaver is in here, Bobby.
The beave is right here and you know what?
It is about building and you know what it's just I'm okay
Yeah, you got the beeper where you say you get the beeper
But he also guessed but what came up before the sea serpents. That's right. Okay
Like the Leviathan is a sea serp the Leviathan you like the Leviathan Bobby
The serpent is very important to me on a few levels, the Ouroboros, the serpent that bites its tail, the symbol of eternity.
Hecate wears a serpent belt and has several serpent epithets, names, Hermes.